# Spiros Xiarchos

Information Systems Specialist

Email: [email protected]
Web: xiarchos.gr

### About Me

Hey there, I'm Spyros and I am a senior student in the Department of Informatics of the Ionian University. During my studies I gained a wide experience in the following fields:

- Constructive wireless networks
- · Hardware maintenance and repairing
- E-shop creation
- Website creation

On top of the technical skills that were built throughout my experience in several companies, I consider myself as a great team player and strong analytical thinker.

# Education

#### **B.Sc.** Informatics

**Ionian University, GR** 10/2015 - Present Specialization in Information Systems.

Main courses follow:

- Strategy & Management of Information Systems
- Analysis & Design of Information
   Systems
- Information Systems & Supply Chain
- Electronic Commerce

# Experience

# Web and Sound Services Freelancer

Freelance

09/2019 - Present

- Web Site Creation and Development
- E-Shop Creation and Development
- Sound Design and Mix

# Hardware Maintainance and Repairing Assistant

Spyretos Computer Service and Repair, Corfu GR

08/2018 - 08/2019

- Hardware Repairing & Maintenance
- IT Technical Support
- Customer Care Services

## Network Expansion Assistant

MNET, Kalamata GR

11/2015 - 08/2018

- Wireless Link Expansion and Maintenance
- IT Tech Support

## A Little More About Me

Apart from the job related interests I'm keen on:

- Tech Savvy
- Vinyl Record Collection
- Music Production
- Hiking
- MotoGP Fan

Spiros Xiarchos - [email protected] - References on request